all right I'm going to talk about the
back extension for a minute here problem
is most people don't come up high enough
and they they hyper extend through the
low back I want a hyp extend at the hips
and I do that through squeezing my
glutes really hard if you do this right
just body weight becomes very very
challenging so most people you know they
they'll do back extensions with all
lumbar they'll they'll be like this just
hinging at the spine well if you want to
work your glutes the most
keep a a rigid spine a neutral spine and
bend at the hips so you want to bend
right here now most people will come up
to here but this last little part from
here to here you know I'm not hypx my
back this is all just squeezing the
glutes to hyperextend the hips so if you
do it this way you know I can get 30
repetitions this way I come down come up
and then from right here most people
would be done but no I come up to here
just by squeezing the glutes
okay you do it and you come up to here
through glute squeeze it becomes way
harder for the glutes again 30 reps For
Me Just Smokes my glutes and gives me an
awesome workout give it a try